(rain pattering)
(thunder rumbling)
(thunder crashing)
(tense somber music)
(water splashing)
(thunder crashing)
(doorknob rattling)
- Stanley?
Open the door, I gotta go!
(banging) Stanley,
open the door!
Let me in!
Stanley, open the door!
(banging)
Open the door!
Let me in!
- [Stan] What?
- Stanley, what are
you doing to yourself?
- What, the hair?
You don't like it?
- Stanley?
- You like it?
- Stanley, what are you-
- Don't call me that, okay?
Don't call me that!
- Don't you think
you're taking this too far?
Stanley-
- You know what, here!
- Stanley!
- Use the toilet.
(thunder crashing)
♪ My tea's gone cold
I'm wondering why I ♪
♪ Got out of bed at all ♪
♪ The morning rain
clouds up my window ♪
♪ And I can't see at all ♪
♪ And even if I could
it'll all be gray ♪
♪ Put your picture on my wall ♪
♪ It reminds me ♪
♪ That it's not so bad ♪
♪ It's not so bad ♪
(thunder crashing)
♪ My tea's gone cold
I'm wondering why I ♪
♪ Got out of bed at all ♪
♪ The morning rain
clouds up my window ♪
♪ And I can't see at all ♪
♪ And even if I could
it'll all be gray ♪
♪ Put your picture on my wall ♪
♪ It reminds me ♪
♪ That it's not so bad ♪
(thunder crashing)
♪ It's not so bad ♪
♪ Dear Slim, I wrote you
but still ain't callin' ♪
♪ I left my cell, my pager, and
my home phone at the bottom ♪
♪ I sent two letters
back in autumn ♪
♪ You must not've got 'em ♪
♪ There probably was a problem ♪
♪ At the post office
or somethin' ♪
♪ Sometimes I scribble addresses
too sloppy when I jot 'em ♪
♪ But anyways, what's been
up, man, how's your daughter ♪
♪ My girlfriend's pregnant too ♪
♪ I'm 'bout to be a father ♪
♪ If I have a daughter,
guess what I'm a call her ♪
♪ I'ma name her Bonnie ♪
(thunder crashing)
♪ I read about your Uncle
Ronnie too, I'm sorry ♪
♪ I had a friend himself over
some who didn't want him ♪
♪ I know you probably
hear this every day ♪
♪ But I'm your biggest fan ♪
♪ I even got the underground
that you did with Skam ♪
♪ I got a room full of your
posters and your pictures, man ♪
♪ I like the you did with
Rawkus too, that was phat ♪
♪ Anyways, I hope
you get this man ♪
♪ Hit me back, just to chat ♪
♪ Truly yours,
your biggest fan ♪
♪ This is Stan ♪
♪ My tea's gone cold
I'm wondering why I ♪
♪ Got out of bed at all ♪
♪ The morning rain
clouds up my window ♪
♪ And I can't see at all ♪
♪ And even if I could
it'll all be gray ♪
♪ Put your picture on my wall ♪
♪ It reminds me ♪
♪ That it's not so bad ♪
♪ It's not so bad ♪
♪ Dear Slim, you still
ain't called or wrote ♪
♪ I hope you have a chance ♪
♪ I ain't mad, I just think
it's up you don't answer fans ♪
♪ If you didn't wanna talk
to me outside your concert ♪
♪ You didn't have to ♪
♪ But you could've signed
an autograph for Matthew ♪
♪ That's my little
brother, man ♪
♪ He's only six years old ♪
♪ We waited in the blistering
cold for you for four hours ♪
♪ And you just said no ♪
♪ That's pretty, man,
you're like his idol ♪
♪ He wants to be
just like you, man ♪
♪ He likes you more than I do ♪
(thunder crashing)
♪ I ain't that mad though ♪
♪ I just don't like
bein' lied to ♪
♪ Remember when
we met in Denver ♪
♪ You said if I write you
you would write back ♪
♪ See, I'm just
like you in a way ♪
♪ I never knew my
father neither ♪
♪ He used to always cheat
on my mom and beat her ♪
♪ I can relate to what
you're saying in your songs ♪
♪ So when I have a day ♪
♪ I drift away and put 'em on ♪
♪ 'Cause I don't
really got else ♪
♪ So that helps
when I'm depressed ♪
♪ I even got a tattoo of
your name across the chest ♪
♪ Bad ♪
♪ Sometimes I even myself
to see how much it ♪
♪ It's like adrenaline ♪
♪ The pain is such a
sudden rush for me ♪
♪ See everything
you say is real ♪
♪ And I respect you
'cause you tell it ♪
♪ My girlfriend's jealous
'cause I talk about you 24/7 ♪
♪ But she don't know you
like I know you, Slim, ♪
♪ No one does ♪
♪ She don't know
what it was like ♪
♪ For people like
us growin' up ♪
♪ You gotta call me man ♪
♪ I'll be the biggest
fan you'll ever lose ♪
♪ Sincerely yours, Stan ♪
♪ P.S. we should
be together too ♪
♪ (thunder crashing) ♪
♪ My tea's gone cold
I'm wondering why I ♪
♪ Got out of bed at all ♪
♪ The morning rain
clouds up my window ♪
♪ And I can't see at all ♪
♪ And even if I could
it'll all be gray ♪
♪ Put your picture on my wall ♪
♪ It reminds me ♪
♪ That it's not so bad ♪
(thunder crashing)
♪ It's not so bad ♪
(car zooming)
♪ Dear Mister I'm Too Good
To Call Or Write My Fans ♪
♪ This'll be the last package
I ever send your ass ♪
♪ It's been six months
and still no word ♪
♪ I don't deserve it ♪
♪ I know you got my
last two letters ♪
♪ I wrote the addresses
on 'em perfect ♪
♪ So this is my cassette
I'm sending you ♪
♪ I hope you hear it ♪
♪ I'm in the car right now ♪
♪ I'm doin' 90 on the freeway ♪
♪ Hey, Slim, I a fifth of ♪
♪ You dare me to drive ♪
(horn honking)
♪ You know the song
by Phil Collins ♪
♪ "In the Air Tonight" ♪
(tires screeching)
♪ About that guy
who could've saved ♪
♪ That other guy from
drowning but didn't ♪
♪ Then Phil saw it all then
at a show he found him ♪
♪ That's kinda how this is ♪
♪ You could've rescued
me from drowning ♪
♪ Now it's too late ♪
♪ I'm on a thousand
now, I'm drowsy ♪
♪ And all I wanted was a
lousy letter or a call ♪
♪ I hope you know I ripped all
of your pictures off the wall ♪
♪ I love you, Slim, we
could've been together ♪
♪ Think about it,
you ruined it now ♪
♪ I hope you can't sleep
and you dream about it ♪
♪ And when you dream I
hope you can't sleep ♪
♪ And you scream about it ♪
♪ I hope your
conscience eats at you ♪
♪ And you can't
breathe without me ♪
♪ See, Slim ♪
♪ I'm tryin' to talk ♪
♪ Hey, Slim, that's
my girlfriend ♪
♪ But I didn't her
throat, I just ♪
♪ See I ain't like you ♪
♪ 'Cause if she suffer
more and then she'll too ♪
♪ Well, gotta go, I'm
almost at the bridge now ♪
♪ Oh, I forgot, how am I
supposed to send this out ♪
(tires screeching)
(car crashing)
♪ Bad ♪
(water splashing)
♪ My tea's gone cold
I'm wondering why I ♪
♪ Got out of bed at all ♪
♪ The morning rain
clouds up my window ♪
♪ And I can't see at all ♪
♪ And even if I could
it'll all be gray ♪
♪ Put your picture on my wall ♪
♪ It reminds me ♪
♪ That it's not so bad ♪
♪ It's not so bad ♪
♪ Dear Stan, I meant
to write you sooner ♪
♪ But I just been busy ♪
♪ You said your
girlfriend's pregnant now ♪
♪ How far along is she ♪
♪ Look, I'm really flattered ♪
♪ You would call
your daughter that ♪
♪ And here's an autograph
for your brother ♪
♪ I wrote it on
the Starter cap ♪
♪ I'm sorry I didn't
see you at the show ♪
♪ I must've missed you ♪
♪ Don't think I did that
intentionally just to diss you ♪
♪ But what's this
you said about ♪
♪ You like to cut
your wrists too ♪
♪ I say that just
clownin' dawg ♪
♪ Come on, how up is you ♪
♪ You got some issues, Stan ♪
♪ I think you need
some counseling ♪
♪ To help your ass from
bouncing off the walls ♪
♪ When you get down some ♪
♪ And what's this ♪
♪ That type of will make me not
want us to meet each other ♪
♪ I really think you and your
girlfriend need each other ♪
♪ Or maybe you just need
to treat her better ♪
♪ I hope you get to
read this letter ♪
♪ I just hope it
reaches you in time ♪
♪ Before you hurt yourself ♪
♪ I think that you'll
be doin' just fine ♪
♪ If you relax a little ♪
♪ I'm glad I inspire
you, but Stan ♪
♪ Why are you so mad ♪
♪ Try to understand ♪
♪ That I do want you as a fan ♪
♪ I just don't want
you to do some crazy ♪
♪ I seen this one on the news ♪
- Stanley Mitchell, along with
♪ A couple weeks ago ♪
- A woman believed to be
♪ that made me sick ♪
- his girlfriend
♪ Some dude was drunk and ♪
- The wet weather is making it
♪ Drove his car over a bridge ♪
- Very difficult
for investigators, but
so far they have ruled
that this is a double
murder-suicide.
♪ And in the car
they found a tape ♪
♪ But they didn't
say who it was to ♪
♪ Come to think about ♪
♪ His name was ♪
♪ It was you ♪
- Damn.
(thunder crashing)
(rain pattering)